Inventory of the W. H. (William Harold) Hutt Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- "The American Tradition and the Great Society," Philadelphia Society national meeting, Chicago, Illinois (1967 March 31 - April 1), 1959-1973. (Box-folder 39: 1-2)
  Includes lists of attendees and papers presented, and program. Also includes articles, brochures, clippings, journals, letters, and newsletters relating to education, international transfer of technology, Keynesianism, labor and foreign policies, property rights, volunteer army, and welfare system
- Articles by others on Keynesianism, New Republic, 1973 (Folder 39: 3)
- Mont Pelerin Society 15th general meeting, Stresa, Italy, 1965 September 3-8. (Folder 39: 4)
  Includes list of participants, notes, papers by others (including Milton Friedman), and program
- Writings by William Hutt (Box 40)
  - Miscellaneous omissions for reconsideration, undated. (Folder 40: 1)
  - Idle Resources, undated. (Folder 40: 2)
    Retyped manuscripts
  - "Praxeological Aspects of Preferred Idleness and Withheld Capacity,", undated (Folder 40: 3)
  - "Colour Bar,", undated. (Folder 40: 4)
- Study of industrial location by others, undated (Folder 40: 5)
- Correspondence, 1961-1966. (Folder 40: 6)
  Includes articles, including one on the working of the electoral system; brochure; notes and reading list for a class on the economics of South Africa; program of the panel at the Philadelphia Society national meeting on civil rights and individual responsibilities; and newsletter, Congress Conservative, on minimum wage
- Collection of articles by William Hutt and others, 1962-1970. (Folder 40: 7)
  Relates to automation, entrepreneurship in different countries, evaluation of alternative plans, and role of government labor monopoly policy
- "International Money," William Hutt, undated. (Folder 40: 8)
  Draft fragment
- "Education of the State," William Hutt, undated. (Folder 40: 9)
  Draft
- "Personal Characteristics of Effective and Successful Executive,", undated.
  Drafts
- Articles on "The Social Responsibilities of Management," and "Job Evaluation," by William Hutt, undated (Box 40)
- Reviews of books by William Hutt and others, 1963-1964.
  Includes a letter, 1964
- Collected articles. Arranged by first letter of author's surname (Box 41)
  - D, 1951-1973 (Folder 41: 1)
  - E, 1966-1971 (Folder 41: 2)
  - F, 1933-1977 (Folder 41: 3-4)
  - O, 1962-1977 (Box-folder 42: 1)
  - P, 1927-1976 (Folder 42: 2-3)
  - J, 1948-1977 (Box-folder 43: 1)
  - K, 1954 (Folder 43: 2)
  - L, 1938-1978 (Folder 43: 3)
- "The Austrian School"--History of economic thought, William Hutt, undated (Folder 43: 4)
- Articles by William Hutt (Box 43)
  - "The Cape-Colored People Today,", undated
  - "Two Studies in the Statistics of Russia,", 1945
  - "Unanimity versus Non-Discrimination (as Criteria for Constitutional Validity),", 1966
- Miscellaneous articles by others, 1955-1977
- Collected articles. Arranged by first letter of author's surname (Box 44)
  - B, 1920-1978 (Folder 44: 1-3)
  - H, 1937-1978 (Box-folder 45: 1-3)
- Writings by William Hutt (Box 46)
  - "Seeds of Change in South Africa,", undated (Folder 46: 1)
  - "The Strike-Threat and Inflation,", undated (Folder 46: 2)
  - "Latin American Free Trade Association and the Evolution of the Andean Group from within It,", undated. (Folder 46: 3)
    Includes outline, reviews, and tables
  - "Exploitation: Shut-In and Shut-Out,", undated (Folder 46: 4)
  - "Differentials," chapter XI, The Strike-Threat System, undated (Folder 46: 5)
  - "Hutcheson and Adam Smith,", undated. (Folder 46: 6-10)
  - "Alfred Marshall," lectures [?], Economics Department, undated (Folder 46: 11-12)
  - "The Aggregate Demand Fallacy," article about Keynesianism for Economics 41, undated (Folder 46: 13)
  - "Industrial Revolution," article, undated (Folder 46: 14)
  - A Rehabilitation of Say's Law, 1975. (Folder 46: 15)
    Includes preface, definitions, introduction, and chapters I-XIII
  - Article, part III, relating to inflation and wages, undated (Folder 46: 16)
  - Theory of Idle Resources, 2nd edition, 1975 [?]. (Folder 46: 17)
    Includes preface and draft chapters
  - Phelps Brown--Article, "The Economics of Labour,", undated (Folder 46: 18-19)
  - Notes, undated (Box 46)
  - Papers by students, 1977
- Article by William Hutt evaluating Patinkin's method in his book, Money, Interest, and Prices, undated (Box-folder 47: 1)
- "The Political Factor in Monetary Policy,", undated (Folder 47: 2)
- Miscellany, 1962-1967. (Folder 47: 3)
  Addresses, articles about currency, and a letter
- Letters--Resignation from Rampart College, Larkspur, Colorado, 1965-1967. (Folder 47: 4)
  Includes a brochure for Rampart College Graduate School
- Addresses by William Hutt, 1936-1950. (Folder 47: 5-7)
  Includes letters, memorandum, and miscellany
- Weighted franchise--Articles by William Hutt and others, 1949-1962 (Folder 47: 8)
- Miscellany, 1928-1950. (Folder 47: 9)
  Includes articles by William Hutt and others, clippings, 1930-1931, and letters. Includes 2 photographic prints depicting unidentified individuals, undated
- Memorandum and articles of association--The Individualist Bookshop, Ltd., 1926 (Box 47)
- Writings by William Hutt (Box 48)
  - "Malthus, James Mill, Say, Ricardo,", undated (Folder 48: 1)
  - "Mercantilism"--Lecture notes for history of economic thought course, undated (Folder 48: 2-6)
  - "Monetary Theory"--Materials, 1972-1974. (Folder 48: 7)
    Includes articles, clippings, notes, report, statistical data, and survey
  - A Rehabilitation of Say's Law, (1975) [?]
    - Photocopies, undated (Folder 48: 8)
    - "Say's Law Restated," chapter II, undated (Folder 48: 9)
  - "The Neutrality of the Market"--Market and Keynesian system, part IV, undated (Folder 48: 10)
  - Articles relating to urban renewal, undated (Folder 48: 11)
- Correspondence (out), 1986 September - 1987 August (Folder 48: 12)
- Humane Studies Review, undated (Box-folder 49: 1)
- Correspondence.
  - In
    - 1985 January - November (Folder 49: 2)
    - 1985 December - 1986 August (Folder 49: 3)
    - 1986 September - 1987 September (Folder 49: 4)
  - Out, 1985 January - November (Folder 49: 5)
- "Apartheid,", 1986 and undated. (Folder 49: 6)
  Includes a cover letter, 1986
- "W. H. Hutt's Contributions in Economics, Politics, and Philosophy," sponsored by The Center for Education and Research in Free Enterprise, Texas A&M University, Dallas, Texas, 1987 September 18-20. (Folder 49: 7)
  Conference papers, memorandum, and program
- Calendars with notations
  - 1986 (Folder 49: 8)
  - 1987 (Folder 49: 9)
- Who's Who, 1987. (Folder 49: 10)
  Biographical information on William Hutt
- Social Science Quarterly--Letters, 1986, and reviewer's comments on "The Economics of the Call---,", undated (Folder 49: 11)
- Program for constitutional change--Letters about the African National Congress, 1987 (Folder 49: 12)
- A Rehabilitation of Say's Law--Letters to declare the book out of print, 1985 (Folder 49: 13)
- List of William Hutt's selected contributions, undated (Folder 49: 14)
- Publications file
  - "The Impoverishers--A Postscript,", 1985-1987 (Folder 49: 15)
  - "Trade Unions and the Free Market,", 1987 (Folder 49: 16)
  - "The Myth of Labor's Disadvantage,", 1987 (Folder 49: 17)
  - "The Power of Labor Unions,", 1987 (Folder 49: 18)
  - "Economics in One Paragraph,", 1987 (Folder 49: 19)
  - "The Market versus the State,", 1987 (Folder 49: 20)
- Correspondence (out), 1985 December - 1986 August (Box-folder 50: 1)
- Writings by William Hutt--Draft chapters
  - "The Keynesian Claim" and "Keynes: The Personal Factor,", undated (Folder 50: 2)
  - "The Political Appeal of Keynesian Doctrine," "The Academic Appeal of Keynesian Doctrine," and "The Nature of the Keynesian Thesis,", undated
  - "Consequences of the Keynesian Remedy," "The Nature of Co-ordination through the Price System," "The Cost and Pains of Non-Inflationary Co-ordination," "The Social Purpose of Price Changes," "Keynesianism and Orthodoxy," and "Keynes and Laissez-Faire,", undated (Folder 50: 3)
  - "The Nature of Money," "The Concepts of Inflation and Deflation," "Keynes Notion of True Inflation," "Income and Its Generation," "Are Price Adjustments Self Frustrating?" "The Nature of Consumption and Saving," "The Consumption Fallacy," "The Marginal Propensity to Consume," and "The Multiplier,", undated (Folder 50: 4)
  - "The Keynesian Harvest," "The Acceleration Fallacy," "Depression and Boom," "Capital Saturation," "The Say Law," "Keynes and Monetary Nationalism," "Anticipated Inflation," and "The Retreat,", undated. (Folder 50: 5)
    Includes list of references
  - Drafts on Keynes, undated (Box 50)
- Articles by Milton Friedman and others, biographical information about William Hutt, clippings relating to Mexico, South Africa, tax reform, and other issues, 1985 March - October (Box-folder 51: 1)
- Contributions of William Hutt to the Dallas Morning News, 1985. (Folder 51: 2)
  Includes articles relating to situations in Nicaragua and South Africa involving apartheid, imports, and exports
- A Rehabilitation of Say's Law--Page proofs, undated (Folder 51: 3)
- Mont Pelerin Society (Box 51)
  - 9th meeting, University of Princeton, New Jersey, 1958 September 8-13.
    Clippings, conference program, list of members, papers, and schedule
  - 14th meeting, Semmering, Austria, 1964 September 7-12.
    Final list of participants, letters, papers, and program
  - 16th meeting, Viche, France, 1967 September 11-16.
    Lists of papers and publications from the Institute of Economic Affairs, notes, and program
- Publication file (Box 52)
  - Letters about publishing William Hutt's autobiography, 1987 (Folder 52: 1)
  - The Economics of the Colour Bar, 1986-1987 (Folder 52: 2-3)
    submitted to Institute of Economic Affairs (IEA). Includes correspondence relating to publication
  - "The Myth of Labor's Disadvantage,", undated (Folder 52: 4)
  - "Trade Unions and the Free Market,", undated. (Folder 52: 5-6)
    Includes a publication copy and a letter from William Hutt to David L. Prychitko
  - "The Minimum Wage: A Major Cause of Poverty,", undated. (Folder 52: 7)
    Includes letter, 1987, and receipt for honorarium from Ludwig von Mises Institute, undated
  - Foreword to "The Cost of Labour,", 1987 and undated. (Folder 52: 8)
  - "The Market versus the Press,", 1987 April 16. (Folder 52: 9)
    Includes a list of major contributions by William Hutt, undated
  - "The Power of Labor Unions," part I, undated. (Folder 52: 10)
    Publication copy
- "The Market versus the State," William Hutt, undated. (Box-folder 53: 1)
- Articles by others, bulletin, journals, lectures, memoranda, and reviews of books, 1927-1978. (Folder 53: 2-3)
  Relates to class struggle in South Africa and freedom of choice, conservation of resources, distributive justice, economic nationalism, health care and public welfare, socialism, study, tax proposals and federal finances, urban renewal, and related materials
- Writings by others
  - "The Prince" by Nicolò Machiavelli--Translated by Leo Paul S. de Alvarez, undated (Folder 53: 4)
  - "TV: From Monopoly to Competition,", 1962 (Box 53)
  - Paper and research monograph, 1966-1968
  - Area economic survey of the Baffin Island--East Coast and Northern Foxe Basin, 1965-1966
- Writings by William Hutt (Box 54)
  - "Economists and the Public: A Study of Competition and Opinion,", undated (Folder 54: 1)
  - Conclusion of "Strike-Threat System," Chapter XIX (duplicate), undated (Folder 54: 2)
  - "Bargaining Power Concept"--The Theory of Collective Bargaining, chapter V, undated (Folder 54: 3)
  - Note by William Hutt to members of the National Taxation Limitation Committee, undated (Folder 54: 4)
  - "Keynesianism"--Old material, undated (Folder 54: 5)
  - "The Consumption Fallacy,", undated (Folder 54: 6)
  - "Credo,", undated (Folder 54: 7)
- A Rehabilitation of Say's Law, 1975 and undated (Box 54)
  - Preface and introduction
  - "Definitions"
  - "Say's Law Restated"
  - "Further Objections to Say's Law"
  - "The Multiplier"
  - "The Marginal Propensity to Consume"
  - "The Concept of Withholding"
  - "Unemployment Disequilibrium"
  - "The True Multiplier"
  - "The Alleged Hiatus"
  - "Yeager's Interpretation"
  - "Effective Demand in Relation to Saving Preference and Liquidity Preference"
  - "The Hiatus--A Different Interpretation"
  - "Pricing for Market Clearance"
  - "Sub-Optimal Employment and Chronic Unemployment"
  - "Harry G. Johnson's View of Pre-Keynesian Orthodoxy"
- "Twelve Thoughts on Inflation,", undated
  Foreword
- Fragments of writings relating to industrial policy, undated
- Articles by Friedrich Hayek, Thomas Sowell, and others, and remarks about miscarriage of democratic ideal, knowledge and decisions, monetarism, and review of A Rehabilitation of Say's Law, 1975 and undated (Box 54)
- Address by the president relating to the cause of freedom in Central America; memorandum, newsletters, and miscellany relating to retirement, community spirit, future right to work; and schedules of the United States Congress, 1977-1987
- "The Economics of Fisheries," proceedings of a roundtable organized by the International Economic Association, sponsored by the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations, Rome, 1956 September
- Writings by William Hutt (Box 55)
  - A Rehabilitation of Say's Law, 1975 and undated. (Folder 55: 1)
    Includes "Further Objections to Say's Law," "The Concept of Withholding," "Unemployment Disequilibrium," "The True Multiplier," "The Alleged Hiatus," "Yeager's Interpretation," "Effective Demand in Relation to Saving Preference and Liquidity Preference," "The Hiatus: A Different Interpretation," "Pricing for Market Clearance," "Sub-Optimal Employment and Chronic Unemployment," "Harry G. Johnson's View of Pre-Keynesian Orthodoxy," "The Position of the Prevailing Orthodoxy of the 1920s and 1930s," and "Some Aspects of Edwin Cannan's Orthodoxy"
  - "Some Special Cases of Investors' Exploitability,", undated (Folder 55: 2)
  - "Exploitation of Investors,", undated (Folder 55: 3)
  - "The Strike-Threat and Inflation,", undated (Folder 55: 4)
  - "Labor Policy and Labor's Disadvantage in Bargaining,", undated (Folder 55: 5)
  - "The Nature of the Strike,", undated (Folder 55: 6)
  - "Labor's Bitter Struggle,", undated (Folder 55: 7)
  - Untitled and unidentified writings relating to labor issues, undated (Folder 55: 8)
- Videorecordings (Box 55)
  - William Hutt's lecture on "Collective Bargaining,", undated
    (lecture 1, copy 3). One U-matic videocassette and a brochure
  - "A Time for Candor about My Father's Business," African National Congress, undated.
    One VHS videocassette
- Writings by William Hutt (Box 56)
  - "The Keynesian System,", undated. (Folder 56: 1)
  - "The Economics of Transportation" and "The Nature of Coordination through the Price System,", undated. (Folder 56: 2)
    Includes fragments
  - A Rehabilitation of Say's Law, 1975. (Folder 56: 3)
    Preface and list of contents
  - "Exploitation by Shutting out or Shutting In,", undated (Folder 56: 4)
- Miscellany, 1970-1983. (Folder 56: 5-9)
  Includes articles, letters, list of attendants, and program for a meeting
- Writings on the labor situation, William Hutt, undated (Folder 56: 10)
- Petro project summary, undated (Folder 56: 11-12)
- Writings by William Hutt (Box 56)
  - "Twelve Thoughts on Inflation,", undated.
  - "Inflation,", undated
  - "The Face and Mask of Unionism,", 1983
  - Galley proofs--"Keynesian Episode: A Reassessment,", undated
- Article by Brian Inglis, undated
- Preface to second edition of a book that deals with the dis-coordination of the price system originating from private or collective sectionalism, undated (Box-folder 57: 1)
- Economists and the Public (1936), 1963-1965. (Folder 57: 2)
  Extracts from reviews. Includes articles and reviews of other books, such as Keynesianism--Retrospect and Prospect, Strike-Threat System, and Economics of the Colour Bar
- "The Nature of Liquidity Preference," William Hutt, undated (Folder 57: 3)
- Miscellany, 1964-1982. (Folder 57: 4)
  Fragments of articles, bulletin, clippings, final examination paper, letters, list of meeting attendees, newsletters, notes, press release, requisition slips, report, reviews of William Hutt's books, statement, and related materials
- Journals--Collection of William Hutt's articles, 1926-1968. (Box 57)
  Includes "Coordination and the Price System: An Examination of the Multiplier and Acceleration Fallacies," 1955 and an issue of The Plebs, 1927
- "The Costs and Pains of Non-Inflationary Co-Ordination," William Hutt, undated
- "Tocqueville's Message for South Africa," William Hutt, undated
- Miscellaneous materials on labor, 1938 and undated.
  Includes clipping, 1938
- The Economics of the Colour Bar, (1964) and undated. (Box-folder 58: 1)
  Includes information about William Hutt, foreword, prefatory note, and preface to the American edition
- "Shared Entrepreneurship," William Hutt, 1979 (Folder 58: 2)
- "Established Differentials," William Hutt, undated. (Folder 58: 3)
- Petro project, undated. (Folder 58: 4)
- "Unions and Distribution," William Hutt, undated. (Folder 58: 5)
- Personal correspondence, 1969-1979. (Folder 58: 6)
  Includes agreement between William Hutt and the Liberty Fund about preparing and publishing a study known as socio-economic projects #2 - #3, 1977, articles by him and others, and comments, 1969-1979
- Material, 1925 and undated. (Box 58)
  Includes writings by William Hutt about Keynesianism and strike-threat, "The Crucial Thesis," "Objections to the Thesis--Preliminary Discussion," "The Bargaining Power Concept," "The Employer Stereotype," "Exploitation--The Shut-In and Shut-Out," "Labor's Bitter Struggle," Foreword to the "Twelve Thoughts on Inflation," "Nature of the Strike," "Are Price Adjustments Self-Frustrating?" "The Poor Who Were with Us-A Reply," "The Corporation as a Form of Competition," and others
- Writings by William Hutt (Box 59)
  - "The Principle of Social Justice,", undated (Folder 59: 1)
  - "Example of the Underdeveloped Areas,", undated (Folder 59: 2)
  - Politically Impossible?, 1971. (Folder 59: 3)
    Full scripts
  - "Democracy and Consumers' Sovereignty,", undated (Folder 59: 4)
  - "Codetermination,", undated (Folder 59: 5-7)
  - "Contractual Incomes under Market Determination,", undated (Folder 59: 8)
  - Drafts relating to the critique of labor policy, undated (Folder 59: 9)
  - "Labor's Disadvantage in Bargaining,", undated. (Folder 59: 10-11)
    Includes list of contents and drafts
  - "Are Labor Unions Aristocracies?", undated (Folder 59: 12-13)
  - "The Neglected Victims,", undated (Folder 59: 14)
  - "Economizing Displacement,", undated (Folder 59: 15)
  - A Rehabilitation of Say's Law, 1975. (Folder 59: 16)
  - "The Economics of Labor Unions,", 1978 December. (Folder 59: 17)
    Discarded [?]
  - Drafts of writings about poverty, undated (Box 59)
  - "The Yugoslavian System,", undated (Box-folder 60: 1)
  - "Vision of a No-Strike Era,", undated (Folder 60: 2-3)
  - "The Function of Losses and Profits" and "Productivity and Wage Rates,", undated (Folder 60: 4)
- Clippings and miscellany, 1933-1984 (Folder 60: 5-6)
- Miscellany, 1982 and undated. (Box 60)
  Includes notes by William Hutt [?] and letter file
- Clippings and miscellany, 1947-1984 (Box-folder 61: 1-4)
- Hearing transcript, 1980-1982. (Folder 61: 5)
  Includes William Hutt's letters to Dan C. Heldman and comments on the evidence, 1982
- Copy for Keynesianism incorporated, undated. (Folder 61: 6)
- "Keynesianism"--Drafts, William Hutt, undated (Folder 61: 7)
- Clippings, 1974-1987 (Box-folder 62: 1)
- Articles by William Hutt and others, and related information in various journals, 1933-1980 (Box 62)
- "Economic Aspects of Municipal Trading," William Hutt, Institute of Town Clerks of Southern Africa 3rd annual conference, 1950
- Photocopies of journals with William Hutt's articles, 1952-1968
- Correspondence--H, 1972-1983. (Box-folder 63: 1)
  Includes correspondents with surnames not beginning with "H"
- Ralph Harris, 1969-1980. (Folder 63: 2)
  Includes letters and press release
- Congressional Record, 1982 (Box 63)
- Government and the Market Economy: An Appraisal of Economic Policy since the Election by Samuel Brittan, 1970 [?]
- Videorecordings. William Hutt's lectures, undated. (Box 63)
  One on Keynesianism and one titled, "The Economic Consequence of Keynesian Economic Policies." Two U-matic videocassettes
- Proposed socio-economic and legal research projects, Institute for Labor Policy Analysis, Wake Forest University, Winston-Salem, North Carolina, undated (Box-folder 64: 1)
- Unsorted correspondence, 1980-1982. (Folder 64: 2)
  Includes transcripts of court proceedings
- Seminars to be held in the near future, 1983-1984. (Folder 64: 3)
  Brochures and letter
- Heritage Foundation--Bulletins, 1983. (Folder 64: 4)
  Includes notes, undated
- Z. S. Gurzynski, 1972-1981. (Folder 64: 5)
- Dan C. Heldman, 1981-1982. (Folder 64: 6)
  Letters from William Hutt
- Correspondence (G-H), 1936-1983. (Folder 64: 7-8)
  Includes clippings and related materials
- Notes, undated (Box 64)
- "Distributive Justice and Colour Antagonism" and "Wage Fixation and the Coloured People," articles by William Hutt, undated
- Review by William Hutt of Alexander Stewart, The World, the West and Pretoria, undated
- Miscellaneous correspondence and telegram, 1976-1982.
  Includes William Hutt's letter to the U.S. President, 1977 August 29
- A Rehabilitation of Say's Law, William Hutt, 1975. (Box-folder 65: 1)
- Keynesianism--Retrospect and Prospect, William Hutt, 1963. (Folder 65: 2)
  Early revision
- William Hutt, 1943-1987. (Folder 65: 3)
  Correspondence with Friedrich Hayek and others, curriculum vitae, list of selected contributions, memorandum, reviews of the Economics of the Colour Bar and Keynesianism--Retrospect and prospect, rough drafts, and notes
- "The Rate of Interest Fallacy," William Hutt, undated. (Folder 65: 4)
  Rough drafts
- T. H. Kelly, 1951 [?]. (Folder 65: 5)
  Article, "Education and Training of Business Managers"
- Memoranda to the Schumann Committee by Ralph Horwitz and Z. S. Gurzynski, undated. (Folder 65: 6)
  Concerns the rating standard and choices of locations for the South African Railways
- Materials, 1963-1982. (Box 65)
  Articles by William Hutt on "Individual Freedom and Strike-Threat Duress" and others relating to mixed economy, relationship between the United States and South Africa, and related issues. Includes clippings, letters, newsletter, retirement program, and study, "Guide to the Conduct and Management of Election Campaigns," prepared by the Progressive Party of South Africa
- Heritage Foundation, 1978-1982. (Box-folder 66: 1)
  Newsletters and William Hutt's letter to William Simon, 1978 October 18
- Correspondence.
  - General
    - I, 1966-1983 (Folder 66: 2)
    - J, 1961-1984 (Folder 66: 3)
    - K, 1965-1983 (Folder 66: 4)
    - L, 1951-1981 (Folder 66: 5)
    - L-O, 1941-1981 (Folder 66: 6)
    - Mc-Mac, 1969-1978 (Folder 66: 7)
    - Ma-Mi, 1965-1982 (Folder 66: 8)
  - Middleman, H. W., 1980-1981 (Folder 66: 9)
  - Mises Ludwig von, 1956 (Folder 66: 10)
  - Morrison Robert S., 1971-1981 (Folder 66: 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971-1983 and undated (Box 66)
- Miscellany, 1978-1981 and undated
- Correspondence (Box 67)
  - General
    - Mo-Mz, 1969-1983 (Folder 67: 1)
    - N, 1966-1983 (Folder 67: 2)
    - O, 1973-1981 (Folder 67: 3)
    - P, 1970-1982 (Folder 67: 4)
    - P-R, 1936-1983 (Folder 67: 5)
    - Ra-Ri, 1971-1981 (Folder 67: 6)
  - National Right to Work Legal Defense Foundation, Inc., 1981 (Folder 67: 7)
  - Palyi, Melchior, 1963-1964 (Folder 67: 8)
  - Petro project, 1975-1982 (Folder 67: 9)
  - Philadelphia Society, 1972-1980 (Folder 67: 10)